<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IIIT Delhi</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="interstitial_ad_sample">Interstitial Ad Sample</string>
    <string name="start_level">Level 1</string>
    <string name="next_level">Next Level</string>
    <!-- -
        This is an ad unit ID for an interstitial test ad. Replace with your own interstitial ad unit id.
        For more information, see https://support.google.com/admob/answer/3052638
    <!- -->
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>
    <string name="Language1">हिंदी</string>
    <string name="Language2">English</string>
    <string name="title_activity_menu_navigator">IIIT Delhi</string>
    <string name="iiitd">IIIT Delhi</string>
    <string name="programs">Programs</string>
    <string name="ug_admission">Admission</string>
    <string name="title_iiitd">
        Indraprastha Institute of Information Technology, Delhi (aka. IIIT-Delhi or IIIT-D) was created as a State University by an act of Delhi Government (The IIIT Delhi Act, 2007) empowering it to do research and development and grant degrees. IIIT-Delhi was officially established on 10th June, 2008 as per this notification in the Delhi Gazette. First class (for BTech(CSE) students) was held on 8th September, 2008.
The institute began with its first batch of 60 BTech students in 2008. This first batch graduated in 2012 - the first Convocation took place in November, 2012. By that time, the institute has attracted nearly 30 faculty members, and its academic program consisted of B.Tech., M.Tech. and Ph.D. programs in CSE and ECE. In a relatively short time, it has earned a good reputation in India and abroad for being a center of quality education and research in IT. 2012 turned out be more remarkable year because during the summer of this year, the institute started functioning from its permanent campus in Okhla. Smt. Sheila Dikshit, Chief Minister of Delhi, inaugurated the campus in October, 2012.
    </string>

    <string name="title_programs">
        IIIT-Delhi currently has programs in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), Electronics and Communications Engineering (ECE), Computational Biology (CB) and Mathematics.
        B.Tech in CSE, ECE and CSAM to prepare students to undertake careers involving innovation and problem solving using Information Technology, to undertake advanced studies for research careers in Information Technology and allied areas. M.Tech in CSE, ECE and CB to provide specialized skills for top positions in industry, to get ready for a career in research. PhD in CSE, ECE, CB and Mathematics to focussed on top-class research. In addition to above, IIIT-Delhi also has an option to obtain Dual Degree (B.Tech and M.Tech) in CSE and ECE.
    </string>

    <string name="title_ug_admission">
        The admission to B.Tech(CSE), B.Tech(ECE), B.Tech(CSAM) and to some seats of B.Tech(CSD) and B.Tech(ITSS) will be done through Joint Admission Counselling(JAC Delhi). During joint counselling, admissions will be offered to candidates in accordance with IIIT-D merit list in different categories. Detailed instructions for joint counselling will be posted on the counselling site from time to time. The joint counselling portal will be activated around mid-June.
        Admission to some seats of B.Tech(CSD) will be through UCEED as per the details available on UCEED website .
        Admission to some seats of B.Tech(ITSS) will be done through Class XII score.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_hindi_message">आईआईआईटी दिल्ली</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>



    <string name="hind_title_activity_menu_navigator">आईआईआईटी दिल्ली</string>
    <string name="hind_iiitd">आईआईआईटी दिल्ली</string>
    <string name="hind_programs">कार्यक्रम</string>
    <string name="hind_ug_admission">दाखिला</string>
    <string name="hind_title_iiitd">
        दिल्ली सरकार (आईआईआईटी दिल्ली अधिनियम, 2007) के एक अधिनियम द्वारा इंद्रप्रस्थ इंस्टीट्यूट ऑफ इन्फोर्मेशन टैक्नोलॉजी, दिल्ली (उर्फ आईआईआईटी-दिल्ली या आईआईआईटी-डी) को स्टेट यूनिवर्सिटी के रूप में बनाया गया था जो इसे अनुसंधान और विकास और अनुदान की डिग्री देने के लिए सशक्त बना रहा था। दिल्ली गजट में इस अधिसूचना के अनुसार आईआईआईटी-दिल्ली का आधिकारिक तौर पर 10 जून, 2008 को स्थापित किया गया था। प्रथम श्रेणी (बीटेक (सीएसई) छात्रों के लिए) 8 सितंबर, 2008 को आयोजित किया गया था।
        यह संस्थान 2008 में 60 बीटेक छात्रों के अपने पहले बैच के साथ शुरू हुआ था। यह पहला बैच 2012 में स्नातक किया गया था - पहले दीक्षांत समारोह नवंबर 2012 में हुई थी। उस समय तक संस्थान ने करीब 30 फैकल्टी सदस्यों को आकर्षित किया है और इसके अकादमिक कार्यक्रम में शामिल हैं बीटेक, एम.टेक। और पीएच.डी. सीएसई और ईसीई में कार्यक्रम अपेक्षाकृत कम समय में, आईटी में गुणवत्ता शिक्षा और अनुसंधान का केंद्र बनने के लिए भारत और विदेश में अच्छी प्रतिष्ठा अर्जित की है। 2012 में अधिक उल्लेखनीय वर्ष निकला क्योंकि इस साल की गर्मियों में संस्थान ने ओखला में अपने स्थायी परिसर से काम करना शुरू कर दिया। श्रीमती। दिल्ली की मुख्यमंत्री शीला दीक्षित ने अक्टूबर 2012 में परिसर का उद्घाटन किया।
    </string>

    <string name="hind_title_programs">
        आईआईआईटी-दिल्ली में वर्तमान में कंप्यूटर साइंस एंड इंजीनियरिंग (सीएसई), इलेक्ट्रोनिक्स एंड कम्युनिकेशंस इंजीनियरिंग (ईसीई), कम्प्यूटेशनल बायोलॉजी (सीबी) और मैथमैटिक्स में कार्यक्रम हैं।
         सीएसई, ईसीई और सीएसएएम में बी.टेक, सूचना प्रौद्योगिकी और अनुसंधान के क्षेत्रों में सूचना प्रौद्योगिकी और संबद्ध क्षेत्रों में उन्नत अध्ययन करने के लिए नवाचार और समस्या सुलझाने के लिए करियर शुरू करने के लिए छात्रों को तैयार करने के लिए तैयार करते हैं। सीएसई, ईसीई और सीबी में एम.टेक, अनुसंधान में करियर के लिए तैयार होने के लिए, उद्योग में शीर्ष पदों के लिए विशेष कौशल प्रदान करने के लिए। सीएसई, ईसीई, सीबी और गणित में पीएचडी को उच्च-स्तरीय अनुसंधान पर ध्यान केंद्रित करने के लिए। उपर्युक्त के अलावा, आईआईआईटी-दिल्ली में भी सीएसई और ईसीई में दो डिग्री (बी.टेक और एम.टेक) प्राप्त करने का विकल्प है।
    </string>

    <string name="hind_title_ug_admission">
        बीटेक (सीएसई), बीटेक (ईसीई), बीटेक (सीएसएएम) और बीटेक (सीएसडी) और बीटेक (आईटीएसएस) की कुछ सीटों में प्रवेश संयुक्त प्रवेश परामर्श (जेएसी) के माध्यम से किया जाएगा। दिल्ली)। संयुक्त परामर्श के दौरान, विभिन्न श्रेणियों में आईआईआईटी-डी मेरिट सूची के अनुसार अभ्यर्थियों को प्रवेश दिया जाएगा। संयुक्त परामर्श के लिए विस्तृत निर्देश समय-समय पर परामर्श साइट पर पोस्ट किए जाएंगे। संयुक्त परामर्श पोर्टल मध्य जून के आसपास सक्रिय होगा।
         यूसीईईडी वेबसाइट पर उपलब्ध विवरणों के अनुसार बी.टेक (सीएसडी) की कुछ सीटों में प्रवेश यूसीईड के माध्यम से होगा।
         बी.टेक (आईटीएसएस) की कुछ सीटों में प्रवेश कक्षा 12 के माध्यम से किया जाएगा।
    </string>

</resources>
